<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About_us | Data Yarns</title>
    <link>/about_us/</link>
      <atom:link href="/about_us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>About_us</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-uk</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/img/favicon.ico</url>
      <title>About_us</title>
      <link>/about_us/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>/about_us/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/about_us/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are a small team of research consultants with a passion for applied and critical research on social and economic development. We operate in the space between social science, data science and program evaluation to help individuals and organizations make sense of what they do to support planning and positive change. We do so by adapting cutting edge data collection and analysis tools to the needs of our clients which are informed by the social, cultural and economic realities in which they and their target audiences operate. We believe that international organisations can do and should do more to listen to, make sense of and communicate the voices of those whom they ultimately wish to serve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our overall research approach is informed by nuanced views of behaviour and social and organizational change and is responsive to day-to-day demands, and longer-term needs and aspirations of development practitioners their funders, and stakeholders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As individuals we are set apart by our respective areas of foundational expertise in social psychology and information and communication technologies. We are joined together by a common passion for research design and data science and a firm belief on the potential for innovation supported by blending traditional and emerging types of information. We can be contacted at infodatayarns@gmail.com or individually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Portfolio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are interested in and have a track record in developing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital tools for data gathering (such as mobile phones, social media and chatbots) and their application in field experiments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Methodological and analytical frameworks which combine emerging data sources (big data and citizen generated data) with traditional survey data to derive enriched insights on social change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research designs for triangulating large-scale quantitative and ethnographic research (observations, focus and individual interviews) to deepen learning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Approaches for monitoring and evaluation that combine routinely collected administrative information with well-targeted primary data collection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advancing the discussion and practice around on data ethics, security and privacy through the development of specific solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
