<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Data Yarns</title>
    <link>/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-uk</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/img/logo.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are a small team of research consultants with a passion for applied and critical research on social and economic development. We hold PhDs from the LSE in Media and Communications, Social Psychology and Methodology. Collectively, we have more than 30 years of research, teaching and advisory experience in the media-for-development sector. We operate in the space between social science, data science and program evaluation to help individuals and organizations make sense of what they do to support planning and positive social and behaviour change. We do so by adapting cutting edge data collection and analysis tools to the needs of our clients which are informed by the social, cultural and economic realities in which they and their target audiences operate. We believe in the transformational potential of data and advocate that international organisations can do and should do more to listen to, make sense of and communicate the voices of those whom they ultimately wish to serve. You can find more information on our expertise and portfolio in the &lt;a href=&#34;/about_us/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;About us&lt;/a&gt; section.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Ford</title>
      <link>/authors/robert-ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/robert-ford/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
